David Gardiner

♦Stockbridge, GA, United States ♦ Phone: (404) 550 5707 ♦ Email: Dgardi@gmail.com ♦ Github: https://github.com/Dgardi ♦ LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/dgardi

Objective

Junior Full Stack Developer with 10+ years' experience in IT through Helpdesk Management, Field Service Management, Technical Recruiting, and Project Management. Skillful communicator with the ability to effectively collaborate with vendors, customers, and stakeholders to support project initiatives. Seeking to utilize newly developed skills as a Junior Full-Stack Developer.

Education

Clayton State University

Morrow, GA

August 2009 - May 2012

Georgia Institute of Technology

Atlanta, GA

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

March 2022 - June 2022

Experience

Georgia Institute of Technology

Atlanta, GA

Full Stack Web Development Student

March 2022 - June 2022*

- Developed web applications with MERN stack (MongoDB, Express, React, Node.JS) while utilizing GIT version control software.
- Collaborated with team to deliver products. Actively practiced Agile methodologies, developed branched features, resolved merge conflicts.
- Practiced test-driven-development (TDD) using Jest to create mock functions and mock modules.
- Utilized client side & server side APIs. Developed RESTful APIs that communicate via HTTP through CRUD requests.
- Developed CLIs to help manipulate and interact with backend data.

HonorBuilt

Talent Acquisition Specialist – Technical Roles

McDonough, GA June 2019 – Present

- Sourced, Contacted, and Interviewed for Technical Roles ranging from entry level to senior level management.
- Assisted in piloting and configuring new Applicant Tracking Systems (ATS) and one-way video interview platforms.
- Performed background checks, reference checks, and assisted with onboarding (I-9, E-Verify, etc.)
- Worked with hiring managers to realign our interview questions to find better fits for their respective teams, helping reduce turnover.

Sabbatical

HonorBuilt

Frankfurt, Germany/Atlanta, GA

August 2020 – July 2021

- Following my 10-year anniversary at HonorBuilt, I took a sabbatical to backpack through Eastern Europe. Borders shut down due to Covid-19 and ended my sabbatical early.
- After returning to the USA, I worked for Netflix on Stranger Things Season 4 as a Production Assistant.

Helpdesk Manager – Restaurant Support

McDonough, GA April 2016 – August 2020

- Acted as POS Project Manager for international QSR client. Enforced functional requirements for POS/KDS, Coordinated Enterprise level menu database configuration, POS Menu Layout, and KDS Routing. Coordinated with Construction Managers, Business Consultants, and Restaurant Trainers on project phases respectively. Assisted 40+ licensee partners a year for POS Projects in 2018 & 2019.
- Managed Build Team responsible for Imaging Servers, POS Equipment, Hot Spare processing, and RMA processing.
- Managed POS Helpdesk serving 2,000+ restaurants.

HonorBuilt Atlanta, GA

Helpdesk Supervisor – Restaurant Support

October 2015 – April 2016

- Monitor agent's calls and ticket notes to improve quality, minimize errors, identify coaching/training opportunities, and track agent performance.
- Review QA feedback from clients and address questions and concerns as they arise.

- Met with IT Leadership monthly to discuss Helpdesk state and SMART goals.
- Regularly found ways to utilize agents in interdepartmental projects, specifically Field Service and Project Management.
- Met with agents to reinforce vision, common goals, individual goals, discuss performance, impart company culture, and develop strategies.

HonorBuilt Atlanta, GA

Project Coordinator

October 2015 – April 2016

- Assist the Project Manager in managing a portfolio of projects, coordinating with the stakeholders, install teams, trainers, design & construction managers, and subcontractors
- Leverage field experience to help Project Manager determine scope of work, pricing services, projecting resource requirements, establish plans, practices, and procedures for new projects and rollouts.
- Created Statements of Work under the supervision of the Project Manager.
- Provide weekly status updates and maintained high level of communication with Project Manager and Stakeholders.
- Owned a KDS Configuration Project and was able to turn the project into a service generating just approx.
 \$1 Million in annual revenue. Created training docs, knowledge docs, Service Level Agreements (SLAs),
 Key Performance Indicators (KPIs), and more.

Skills

Languages/Libraries/ORMs: HTML, Handlebars, CSS, JavaScript, Express.js, Node.js, jQuery, React,

Database: MongoDB, SQL, MySQL

Software: GIT, Visual Studio Code, Compass, Insomnia, Figma

Deployment: Heroku, GitHub Pages

Other Skills: Object-Documented Mapping, Object Oriented Programming, Model-View Controller

Frameworks.